Guide to the Ray Lyman Wilbur, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0064A
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 1942-1943, Series 27
  - Registrar, March - August 1943 (Box 290, Folder 22)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund: Pending (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund: Requests (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Ro (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Sa (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Sc (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - Se (Box 291, Folder 9)
  - Slavic Languages (Box 291, Folder 10)
  - Sm (Box 291, Folder 11)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 291, Folder 13)
  - Social Science, School of (Box 291, Folder 12)
  - Sororities (Box 291, Folder 14)
  - St (Box 291, Folder 16)
  - Stanford - Forms of Gifts, Trusts, and Bequests (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Associates, September, October, November (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Associates, December, January, February (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Associates, March, April, May (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Associates, June, July, August (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Future (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Ilustrated Review (Box 292, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 292, Folder 10)
  - Statistics (Box 292, Folder 11)
  - Student Hospital Fund (Box 292, Folder 12)
  - Su (Box 292, Folder 13)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 292, Folder 14)
  - T (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity (Box 293, Folder 2)
  - Trustees (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - Tuition (Box 293, Folder 5)
  - U (Box 293, Folder 6)
  - Unique (Box 293, Folder 7)
  - United States, September - February (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - United States, March - August (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - United States Army (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - United States Navy (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - United States Signal Corps (Box 294, Folder 8)
  - V (Box 294, Folder 5)
  - Wa (Box 294, Folder 9)
  - War Courses (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - War Manpower Commission (Box 294, Folder 6)
  - Waves (Box 294, Folder 10)
  - West Memorial Lectureship (Box 294, Folder 11)
  - Wh (Box 294, Folder 12)
  - Wo (Box 294, Folder 13)
  - Women's Council (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - XYZ (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Y.M.C.A & Y.W.C.A (Box 295, Folder 3)
- 1943-1944, Series 28
  - A (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - A.S.S.U. - Chaparral, Hammer & Coffin (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council (Box 298, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Committee (Box 298, Folder 12)
  - Admissions and Advanced Standing, Commission on (Box 298, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board (Box 298, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Committee on Priorities and Coordination of Stanford Appeals (Box 298, Folder 11)
  - Alumni - Deceased (Box 295, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Association (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Clubs of Stanford (Box 295, Folder 11)
  - American Association of Junior Colleges (Box 295, Folder 13)
  - American Council on Education (Box 295, Folder 14)
  - American Red Cross (Box 295, Folder 15)
  - American Shipping Project (Box 295, Folder 16)
  - American Youth for Democracy (Box 295, Folder 17)
  - Anatomy (Box 299, Folder 8)
  - Anatomy - appointments, resignations, leaves (Box 299, Folder 9)
  - Applications for Positions, March - September 1944 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Applications for Positions, September - March 1943-44 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Armed Forces Institute (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - Assistants (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - Association of American Colleges (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - Automobiles - car mileage allowance (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - "B" (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - Bacteriology (Box 299, Folder 10)
  - Bacteriology - appointments, resignations, leaves (Box 299, Folder 11)
  - Belgian American Educational Foundation (Box 296, Folder 11)
  - Biological Sciences (Box 299, Folder 12)
  - Biology - appointments, resignations, leaves (Box 299, Folder 14)
  - Biology - Mumford [Edward P.] Pacific Island research (Box 299, Folder 15)
  - Biology, School of (Box 299, Folder 13)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - Bohemian Club (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Bowling Alleys (Box 296, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts of America (Box 296, Folder 13)
  - Budget (Box 296, Folder 9)
  - Budget - salary and wage scale (Box 296, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee (Box 298, Folder 13)
  - "C" (Box 296, Folder 14)
  - California, University of (Box 296, Folder 15)
  - Central Records Bureau (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - Chaparral (Box 296, Folder 16)
  - Chemistry (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - Chemistry - appointments, resignations, leaves: March to Sept. (Box 300, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry - appointments, resignations, leaves: Sept. to March (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - Circular Letters (Box 296, Folder 17)
  - Civil Aeronautics - source book on aviation (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - Classics (Box 300, Folder 6)
  - College Study Program (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Commencement (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth Club (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Condolence letters (Box 299, Folder 2)
  - Condolence letters, March to September (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Conference Center - Stanford campus (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Congratulations (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - Congratulations, Stanford Presidency: A-F (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Congratulations, Stanford Presidency: F-K (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - Congratulations, Stanford Presidency: K-P (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Congratulations, Stanford Presidency: P-T (Box 297, Folder 9)
  - Congratulations, Stanford Presidency: T-Z (Box 297, Folder 10)
  - Consulting Committee on Undergraduate Studies (Box 298, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Courses (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - D (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Men (Box 300, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Men - appointments, resignations, leaves (Box 300, Folder 8)
  - Dean of Women (Box 300, Folder 9)
  - Dean of Women - appointments, resignations, leaves (Box 300, Folder 10)
  - Deans Committee (Box 298, Folder 16)
  - Defense - S. U. Civilian Defense Council (Box 298, Folder 15)
  - Economics (Box 300, Folder 11)
  - Education - appointments, resignations, leaves (Box 300, Folder 14)
  - Education, School of: March to Sept. (Box 300, Folder 13)
  - Education, School of: Sept. to March (Box 300, Folder 12)
  - Electron Microscope Committee (Box 298, Folder 17)
  - Exceptional Student Committee (Box 298, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Research Club (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Women's Club (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Study (Box 298, Folder 19)
  - Judge George E. Crothers (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Lower Division Committee (Box 298, Folder 20)
  - Men's Faculty Club (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Mothers Club of Stanford University (Box 298, Folder 7)
  - Music, Friends of (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - National Defense Research Committee (Box 298, Folder 21)
  - Public Exercises (Box 298, Folder 22)
  - Public Health Committee (Box 298, Folder 23)
  - Radio Committee and Institute (Box 298, Folder 24)
  - Research, Committee on (Box 298, Folder 25)
  - Rotary Club (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Schedule, Holidays, Examinations, Committee on (Box 298, Folder 26)
  - Scholarship Committee (Box 298, Folder 27)
  - Stanford Clubs (Box 298, Folder 6)
  - University Publications Committee (Box 298, Folder 28)
  - Veteran's Education Committee (Box 298, Folder 29)